{
    "id": "0b3eb5f4cb134475ab42cafdf3d4e0c1",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is ………………… than his neighbors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rich",
                "richer",
                "richest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9de50248aa443ae95fbdb8c46fc8aec"
        },
        {
            "question": "The brides were much ……………… than the grooms.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "young",
                "younger",
                "youngest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc76190af44f42668494eda1a08efee8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is too ………………… to be taught.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "intelligent",
                "more intelligent",
                "most intelligent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07c13b7f6eba473f983474a8220b2fcb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………… than I thought him to be.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "clever",
                "cleverer",
                "cleverest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ccc19ba2184a441bb64503c76a758794"
        },
        {
            "question": "When the old woman became …………………, she began to move about.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stronger",
                "more strong"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "02ece0d736704021a5b6fc6ca71a401a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is much ………………… now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b169f90a95414132bb9441be20270514"
        },
        {
            "question": "The offer was too ………………… to be true.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f0fc87b1ffd45d2987c3b341de1ca9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He fishes with ………………… success than I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "great",
                "greater",
                "greatest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "449098f1d0854ae288d86429da3883fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Shakespeare is the ………………… playwright in English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "great",
                "greater",
                "greatest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eb484128836646aea88b52bd98c64f80"
        },
        {
            "question": "The pain was ………………… than he could bear.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ace2e719fdb149649787308ddfede638"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………… thing of all was that his son was rude to him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "worse",
                "worst"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fcff129f798c4d658907becb821a3b3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane was the ………………… player of the two.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ebfdf88233f47fe80e245da15208b16"
        }
    ]
}